来一份小蛋糕吗
Care for a cupcake?
我们的室外用餐区
Well, our new outdoor seating area
跟宝拉·迪恩去看NBA一样"受欢迎"啊
is about as popular as Paula Deen at an NBA game.
我们还得在外面坐多久啊
How much longer do we have to be out here?
我们好冷
We are cold.
好冷好冷啊
So, so cold.
我都能看见自己呼吸冒烟了
I can see my breath.
我的蛋弟们都冷到缩上胸腔了
And my boys are up by my rib cage.
我能闻到他呼吸的臭味
I can smell his breath.
而我的老蛋们都缩到年轻时的高度了
And my boys are up by where my boys used to be.
这些"顾客"一点帮助都没有
And these customers aren't helping.
我们怎么会觉得阿憨坐镇现场
How could we have thought a strong Han presence
会让这里更有人气呢
would make it more popular?
麦克斯 我放个马后炮
Max, in hindsight,
貌似我们省钱不买暖炉灯
it feels like us not springing for those heat lamps
是个坏主意
was a bad call.
还用你说
Uh, you think?
各位 我尿了一点 暖和身子
Guys, I just peed a little to keep warm.
我也尿了一点
Well, I peed a little
因为我控制不住
'cause I had no choice.
这下好了 他们会被冻在板凳上
Great, they're stuck to the bench.
去拿刮刀救他们吧
Go get the windshield scraper.
在读《美国周刊》杂志吗 厄尔
Reading Us Weekly, Earl?
"明星 与凡人没有不同"
Ooh, "Stars. They're just like us."
如果真的跟我们一样
Well, if they're just like us,
那他们把内裤由里翻外穿的照片在哪呢
where's the picture of them turning their underwear inside out?
卡洛琳把这杂志忘在男厕里的
Caroline left it in the men's room.
现在我说出来自己听到
And as I said that out loud,
我才发现是我跑错进女厕了
I realized that I must have been in the ladies' room.
麦克斯 我快瞎了
I can't see, Max.
麦克斯 我有令人兴奋的好消息
Max, I've got some exciting news!
在我看完上一部《夺宝奇兵》电影后
Eh, I vowed I'd never get excited about anything again
我发誓再也不对事情兴奋了
after that last Indiana Jones.
我在莎莉广告网上找到两盏便宜的暖炉灯
I found us two discount heat lamps on Sherry's list.
这网站跟克雷格广告网差不多
It's like Craigslist, but without the high probability
但碰见疯子杀人魔医科学生的几率低很多
of being murdered by a deranged medical student.
买那暖炉灯的事情呢
And about those lamps?
就省省吧
Uh, no.
我们的室外生意有啥好担心的
We can't worry about our outdoor business.
室内的部分都没啥生意了
We barely have an indoor business.
就你这态度 也永远不会有生意做
And we never will, with that attitude.
我再求你一次
I'm gonna ask you one more time:
听听我们从垃圾堆捡回家的托尼·罗宾斯卡带
please listen to those Tony Robbins tapes we found in the garbage.
姑娘们 明天就是我
Well, girls, tomorrow's the day
期盼了足足三年的日子了
I've been looking forward to for three years.
你终于要去洗牙了吗
You're getting your teeth cleaned?
抱歉 这是我们一直期盼的事情
Sorry, that's what's we've been looking forward to.
我要搬去跟苏菲同居了
I'm moving in with Sophie.
从现在起 约炮只从家里约
From now on, the booty call is coming from inside the house.
我不小心听到了你们的对话
I couldn't help but overhear.
从那么里面都能听到吗
From way back there?
你这耳朵应该多给身体其他部位加油打气
Your ears should give a pep talk to the other parts of your body.
奥列格 如果你搬家需要任何协助
And, Oleg, if you need any help with the move,
欢迎找我帮手哦
might I offer my services?
我的健身教练说我越来越精实了
My trainer Skylar says I'm getting ripped.
是钱包里的钱被他"精实"了吧
Yeah, ripped off by Skylar.
谢啦 阿憨
Thanks, Han.
作为我对你的小小回报
And as a bit of a payback,
今晚我在厨房干活会洗个手
I'll wash my hands back here tonight.
回头见啦 邻居们
See you later, neighbors.
奥列格要搬进楼里
Oleg's moving in?
这是我这辈子碰过最惨的事了
This is the worst thing that's ever happened to me.
与我失去20亿的事并列
And I lost $2 billion.
怎么了 这是好消息啊
What is the problem? This is all good news.
苏菲跟奥列格爱得火热
Sophie an Oleg are in love.
是啊
Yeah!
他们会在各处"火热"
And they'll be in love
比如我们楼梯间
on our stairs,
我们的走廊
in our hallway,
以及洗衣房里的每一寸地方
and on every surface of the laundry room.
而且你懂个毛爱啊 基督徒小处男
What do you know about love anyway, Christian Single?
我知道耶稣会为我安排一个姑娘
I know Jesus has a girl for me.
他必需这么做
He has to.
我泥足深陷那约会网站400大洋那么深了
I'm $400 deep into that damn website.
我们得立个约定
Look, we just make a pact
无论他们在楼上
that no matter what happens upstairs,
还是楼梯间 或洗衣房里做了"什么"
or on the stairs or in the laundry room,
绝对不能让他们入侵我们家
we don't invite it into our apartment.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
外面在下脸盆大雨
It's raining cats and goats out there.
你是指"倾"盆大雨吗
Don't you mean "Cats and dogs"?
一进门就被人纠正的感觉真是爽歪歪啊
Oh, it's so nice to be corrected as you walk in the door.
宝贝
Hey, baby.
你敢相信明天我们就要住在罪里[婚前同居]了吗
Can you believe in 24 hours we'll be living in sin?
不用担心
Oh, don't worry.
我爸妈不知道
My parents don't know.
我明晚会办一场晚餐派对来庆祝
I'm having a dinner party tomorrow night to celebrate.
也因为我还有13斤的牛肉
And also because I have 15 pounds of beef
快要过期了
that's about to go bad.
麦克斯 卡洛琳 你们来吗
So, Max, Caroline, are you in?
苏菲 我们有点忙...
Actually, Sophie, we're busy--
一定到
We'll be there.
有牛肉的事 就是我的事
If there's beef involved, I'm involved.
麦克斯 我们不是才约定好吗
What happened to the pact we just made?
我很不想告诉你
I hate to tell you this--
但如果有天得你与牛肉二选一
if it comes down to you or beef,
我永远都会选牛肉
I'm always going beef.
是莎莉广告网的莎莉打来的
That was Sherry from Sherry's list.
她让我们这么叫她
She makes you call her that.
她说如果我们自己上门取货
She said she's consider charging us $150
灯就只收150块就好
if we pick up the heat lamps themselves.
我也要指控[收费]你三项干扰我看
And I'm charging you with three counts of interrupting
"婴儿坐到有缺陷高脚椅"影片的罪名
this "Baby in a Faulty High Chair" video.
真实生活中有人跌倒了
Someone fell in real life!
你跟我说你能行的
You told me you had it.
我明明是说我不行
I said I didn't have it.
是奥列格跟阿憨在搬家
It's Oleg and Han moving in.
离门边远点
Get away from the door!
那正好在他平视的范围内
Han will see your feet under the door.
他眼睛平视就会看到你的脚
They're right at his eye level.
这就像是恐怖电影《电锯惊魂3》
This is like a horror movie-- Saw III.
因为阿憨弯腰的时候
Because when Han bent over,
我看到了他三英寸股沟
I saw 3 inches of his crack.
所以你把他整条股沟都看完了
So you saw his whole crack?
站一边去
Step away!
麦克斯 开门
Open the door, Max.
我准备要宰了阿憨
I'm about to kill Han,
我知道你一定会想看
and I know you're gonna want to see that.
靠 还真被他说中了
Damn it! He's right.
阿憨 衣服挺可爱啊
Cute outfit, Han.
人家是澳洲"雷霆猛男秀"
Like one of those male strippers
你这是"雷霆萌男秀"
from "No Thunder From Down Under."
这箱也太重了
This is so heavy.
奥列格 你里面装了什么啊
Oleg, what do you have in here?
袜子啊
Socks!
我说真的 阿憨
Really, Han,
你这双手臂只是当摆设用的吧
It's like your arms are only there for decoration.
说句公道话 奥列格的袜子
To be fair, Oleg's socks
里面都挺重[满满精液]的吧
probably have some pretty heavy loads in them.
奥列格 你堆这些垃圾在这里干嘛
Oleg, what is all your junk doing out here?
我好像"闻"到了被囚禁女人的尖叫呢
Do I actually smell girls screaming?
我把东西搬上楼 苏菲说"不准"
I bring things up, Sophie says "No,"
我只好再把东西搬下来
I bring them right back down.
他妈的这破楼就没个电梯吗
Is there no elevator up in this bitch?
奥列格 你忘了拿走你的画
Oleg, you forgot your painting,
这一件东西绝对"不准"进我家
and this one's a definite "No."
苏菲 到目前为止 你还没准过任何东西
Sophie, I haven't gotten a "Yes" yet,
除了准许过我们在浴室洗手台的那场快炮
aside from the quickie we had up against the bathroom sink.
算不上是"快"炮啊
Not such a quickie.
他们把我锁在外面 害我得在卡车上吃午餐
They locked me out and I had to eat my lunch in the truck.
你这样我租搬家卡车的意义在哪呢
Then what was the point of me renting a moving truck?
我是指除了在卡车里的狂野性爱之外
I mean, besides the rough sex we had up against the sides?
他们停路边在车里搞的时候把我锁车外了
They locked me outside on the side of the road for that one.
好吧 我们得先失陪了
Okay, well, we have to go back in.
今晚的牛肉马拉松上见
See you tonight at the beef-a-thon.
不 奥列格
No, Oleg.
或许是我做得不地道了
Maybe I'm being unfair.
你有这么多你钟爱的事物
I mean, you have all this stuff that you like,
而她们有一间公寓
and they have an apartment.
放她们家里吧
Put it in there.
苏菲
Sophie!
今晚八点见
I'll see you at 8:00!
姑娘们 你们说呢
So what do you say, girls?
-绝对不... -用客气
- Absolutely not-- - Yes.
麦克斯 我这疯狂举动是有理由的
Max, there's a method to my madness.
奥列格 能给我们几秒钟吗
Oleg, will you excuse us a second?
顺便帮忙阿憨拿一下那箱子吧
And maybe help Han with that box.
他穿那种裤子 我能看见他就要脱肠了
In those shorts, I can actually see a hernia happening.
不是说好不要招惹他们吗
I thought we weren't getting involved!
如果我们帮忙奥列格
If we help Oleg out,
他就会让我们用他的搬家卡车
he'll let us use the moving truck
去载回我们的暖炉灯
to pick up our heat lamps.
我不是说过不许买吗
I already said "no" to those.
但我们刚才谈过了啊
But we just talked about it!
我根本没在听
I wasn't listening!
那个婴儿脸朝下摔进土豆泥里呢
That baby fell face-down into mashed potatoes.
谁让你答应去参加晚餐
But you said "Yes" to the dinner party,
你牛肉要吃到 我的灯也要买到
so if you get your meat, I get my heat.
你别以为你押韵我就会原谅你
Just because you rhyme doesn't make it okay.
我估计蕾哈娜也是这么跟她男友说的
And I'm pretty sure that's what Rihanna said to Chris Brown.
我们到底是要到哪去找这卖暖炉灯的女人啊
Where are we meeting this chick with the heat lamps?
打从计划生于联盟搬到新泽西后
I haven't gone this far for something I didn't want
我就没为了不想要的东西这么大费周章过了
since Planned Parenthood moved to New Jersey.
我有点晕卡车啊
I'm getting truck sick back here.
大家都以为亚裔开车技术烂 但你比我更烂
You're a worse driver than people assume I am.
快点 让开啊
Come on! Come on!
我们晚餐要迟到了
We're gonna be late to dinner!
你们有兴趣跟我来场
Would any of you be interested in playing
剪刀石头布来决定谁坐后面吗
rock-paper-scissors for a seat up front?
不要
No!
姑娘们 我能问个感情问题吗
Girls, can I ask you a relationship question?
不要
No!
而且我们哪懂什么感情啊
And besides, what would we know about relationships?
这就像问富豪川普
That's like asking Donald Trump
认不认识好的发型师一样
for the name of a good hairstylist.
我想问 她到底是什么意思
I mean, what's the deal with her?
是她让我搬过去同居
She asks me to move in,
却连一张画都不让我挂吗
and then won't even let me have my painting?
也是 苏菲都把牛买下来了
I mean, Sophie already bought the cow.
牛想拉屎就让它拉呗
She might as well let the cow's crap in.
所以你觉得我没错吧
So you're saying I'm right.
不是不是 但我是想...
No, no, but I do think--
你才没有想
No, you don't think,
如果你有动脑想 你现在就会闭上嘴了
or your mouth wouldn't be moving right now.
我只是说
I'm just saying,
他的确是有权利把自己一些东西
he has the right to move some of his stuff
从我们家搬去苏菲家里
into Sophie's apartment and out of ours.
说到他的东西
Speaking of his stuff,
后面有一箱东西
there's something in a box back here
传出震动声呢 现在停了
is humming, and-- oh, it stopped.
又开始了
Oh, it started again.
这是我的仿真人带口部模拟自慰嘴
That's my lifelike mouth with authentic jaw action.
奥列格 看路啊
Oleg, watch the road!
我可不想死前听到最后一个词是"仿真人嘴"
The last words I hear can't be "Lifelike mouth."
一切看起来都很棒哦 苏菲
Everything looks very nice, Sophie.
其实呢
Yeah, see,
其他宾客来之前我不打算说话
I'm not gonna talk until the other guests arrive.
我得把我女主人的光彩留给真的宾客们
I got to save my hostess sparkle for the real guests.
宝贝 我来啦
Hey, baby.
你丫死哪去了
Where the hell have you been?
你这"光彩"挺响亮啊
That was a pretty loud sparkle.
苏菲 迟到都怨我
It's my fault we're late, Sophie--
没关系 坐下吧
It's okay. Just sit down.
你不想知道为什么...
Don't you want to know what I was--
真心不用 我这有一锅炖牛肉
No, really. I got a pot roast over here
比你要说的有意思多了
that's a hell of a lot more interesting.
麦克斯 你来了真是太好了
Max, thank God you're here.
刚才这里无言尴尬到爆
There was so much awkward silence,
我都得用一根香蕉假装有人打电话给我了
I pretended I got a phone call from a banana.
我去冲个澡 很快就好
I'm gonna take a quick shower.
奥列格 晚餐做好了呢
Oh, Oleg, Dinner is ready.
你不够时间去楼下青年旅社洗澡了
You don't have time to run down to the "Y" Now.
我是指在你这里洗
No, I meant I would shower here.
这里吗
Here...
在我浴室里洗吗
In my bathroom?
是啊
Uh...Yeah.
我现在也住这里
I live here now.
对哦
Oh, yeah.
你说得没错
That's right.
想象下这画面
Imagine that.
奥列格 你为什么不直接过来
Hey, Oleg, why don't you just come over here
坐厄尔旁边就好了
and sit next to Earl?
他这么老了 鼻子肯定已经废了
Because he's old and I'm sure his smeller is shot.
苏菲 你绝对得去写本《怎么"娱乐"宾客》的书啊
Sophie, you really must write a "How to entertain" book.
来吧
Here we go:
我奶奶秘传的炖牛肉
Grandma Chinkski's pot roast.
看起来好好吃
This looks amazing.
我冬天时最喜欢吃根菜类植物了
I love a root vegetable in the winter.
就不能默默听我说完吗
Can it ever just be about me?
* 牛 牛 牛 *
* Beef, beef, beef *
* 牛肉 牛 牛 *
* B-beef, b-beef, beef *
干嘛 这是我的牛肉之歌
What? That's my beef song.
我想对苏菲说几句敬酒词
I'd like to make a toast to Sophie.
真贴心
Oh, that's sweet.
但不许敲那杯子
But not with that glass.
那是我奶奶的水晶杯
That's Grandma Chinski's crystal.
宝贝 我祝酒词没说完呢
Baby, I was in the middle of a toast.
抱歉 可是...
Oh, I'm sorry, but...
那是我最珍爱的宝贝
those are my favorite thing!
我奶奶用我两个弱智的表亲换来的呢
Grandma Chinski traded two of my slow cousins for those.
你知道吗 说来好笑
Well, you know, it's funny.
我也有个最珍爱的宝贝
I have a favorite thing too.
我何不现在就去把它取来呢
In fact, why don't I just go and get it?
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我终于要见到罗尼·安迪生了
I'm about to meet Loni Anderson!
谁能帮我把叉子拿起来喂我一下
Can someone help me lift up my fork?
因为搬家 我的双臂现在还酸得不行
My arms are still sore from the move.
张开嘴
Open up.
换个人来喂阿憨吧
Someone else has to feed Han.
他刚舔到我的小尾指了
He just licked my pinky.
厄尔 你在那边干嘛呢
Earl, what are you doing over there?
跟红极一时的R&B巨星叙旧啊
Just hanging out with R&B sensation,
玛丽·简·大麻
Mary J.-juana.
那正好
Oh, good.
你的状态正适合徒手喂食一个30岁的小爷们
So you're in the right mind-set to hand-feed a 30-year-old man.
不不不不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
她说的是波兰语的"不"吧
I think that's Polish for "No."
就要 苏菲
Yes, Sophie.
这是我的画
It's my painting.
口误了 应该是我们的画
Excuse me--our painting.
我要把它挂到我们的墙上
And it's going up on our wall.
是我大麻抽多了
Is it me,
还是派对气氛超剑拔弩张啊
or is this party tense as hell?
我觉得苏菲和奥列格可能过不了这关啦
I don't think Sophie and Oleg are gonna make it.
啊哦 我是不是把心声都说出来了
Uh-oh. Am I talking out loud right now?
我说了 我不想让这玩意挂我家里
I told you, I don't want that thing in here.
我不懂 不就是副画吗
I don't understand. It's just a painting.
到底是有多差啊
What's so bad about it?
我的上帝呀
Oh, my God.
正点吧
Nice, huh?
我自己画的
I did it myself.
这可是数字油画
It's a paint-by-numbers.
你是说这是"数字普京"吧
You mean it's a Putin-by-numbers.
为什么他的奶头这么大
Why are his nipples so big?
我觉得不是很大呀
They don't seem that big to me.
看来我是抽太嗨了
Oh, I am too high for this.
而我是还不够嗨
I'm not high enough.
在我的文化里 大奶头代表权利和财富
In my culture, big nipples mean power and wealth.
而在我们的文化 大奶头就代表
In our culture, big nipples means,
"穿着T恤去泳池卖骚"
"Wears a t-shirt in the pool."
好了
There.
我喜欢
I like it.
给这个房间增添了某种风情
Adds a certain something to the room.
每一面墙都需要奶头
Every wall needs nipples.
这样男人才知道看哪里
So a guy knows where to look.
谢谢你劝我这么做 卡洛琳
Thank you for telling me to do this, Caroline.
是她的主意吗
She did?
我很想起身逃跑 但我的双腿已经累到无力
I'd get up and run, but my legs are like taffy.
跟姐说实话
Seriously,
是你让他把那玩意挂我墙上的吗
you told him to hang that thing up?
天地良心 建议他这么做之前
In fairness, I had not seen the painting
我根本没见过这幅画
when I suggested something like that.
我是说 我懂
I mean, I get it.
这幅画很棒
It's gorgeous.
但它跟我家的装修风格不搭
But it doesn't go with the decor.
什么
What?
我的画让你销魂的室内外秋千黯然失色了吗
Is it throwing off this gorgeous outdoor-indoor swing?
老娘要用这把切肉刀宰了你
I'll cut you with the carving knife!
谁也不可以宰了谁
Nobody is cutting anyone.
尤其不许宰我
Especially not me.
你就不会学着点吗
Do you never learn?
像我这样把牛肉偷藏进餐巾里
Just put some beef in your napkin like I did,
然后赶紧溜之大吉
and let's get out of here.
苏菲 是你让我搬进来
Sophie, you asked me to move in.
你猜怎么着 我搬进来了
Guess what? I moved in.
是啊 我让你搬进来
Yes, I asked you to move in,
但是我没说让大奶头普京也搬进来
but not with big weird-nipple Putin.
奶头一般有多大啊
Well, how big are nipples supposed to be?
因为...算了 当我没问
'Cause--never mind.
你到底在闹什么呀
And what's your problem anyway?
我有给你个抽屉放东西啊
I gave you a drawer.
这个
This!
各位请看 这就是我的抽屉
This is my drawer, everybody.
这么小有毛用
What good is this?
老子甚至连一副性虐口塞球都塞不进去
I can't even get one of my ball gags in there.
你说要抽屉 老娘给了你一个抽屉
You asked for a drawer, I gave you a drawer!
再说了 谁会需要12副口塞球啊
And who needs 12 ball gags anyway?
所以你现在不喜欢口塞球了吗
Oh, so now you don't like ball gags?
你这女人到底是谁啊
Who are you, lady?
我来告诉你我是谁
I'll tell you who I am--
我是把普京扔进垃圾桶的女人
I'm the lady who's "Putin" this is the trash!
你敢扔我的画 我就扔你的杯子
You trash that, I'll trash this.
不许
Oh, no.
你觉得我奶奶的水晶杯
Oh, you think you're gonna break
会有一个烂在你手里吗
one of Grandma Chinski's glasses?
别想 如果烂了 那也一定是我摔烂的
No, if anyone's gonna break one, it's gonna be me!
这让我想起了我第二段婚姻的前半阶段
This reminds me of the first half of my second marriage,
以及我第三段婚姻的后半阶段
and the second half of my third marriage.
苏菲 我受够了
Sophie, I'm done.
正如你在我们第一次约会时说的那样
And as you said to me on our first date,
"我不知道我还'承受'得了多少"
"I don't know how much more of this I can take."
这顿饭真有意思
Fun party.
完全没有半点尴尬
Not awkward at all.
不过我得走了
I should get going though.
明天还得早起去...叫什么来着
Got to be up early for-- what's a thing?
教堂吗
Church?
* 牛 牛 牛 *
* Beef, beef, beef *
* 牛肉 牛 牛 牛 *
* B-beef, beef, beef, beef *
昨晚的晚餐真的很抱歉
Sorry about that dinner party last night.
我昨晚有一点点小失控
It kind of got away from me a little bit.
但我真的很感激你们俩能早起
But I really appreciate you getting up early
帮我把奥列格的东西搬回去
and helping me move Oleg's stuff back.
其实我是觉得有一小部分是我的错
I just actually feel like this is a little bit my fault--
你不是吧
Seriously!
就不能默默听我说完吗
Can it ever just be about me?
话说我们到底要把他的东西运哪儿啊
Hey, um, where are we taking his stuff anyway?
我觉得慈善二手店可不会要
I don't think Goodwill will take a love seat
一张满是爱液的双人椅
that's actually covered in love.
我在想
Well, I was thinking,
既然我和奥列格
you know, since Oleg and I
的确有过一段刻骨铭心的爱情
really did have something special,
我在想要不要把他的东西
I was thinking I would just take his stuff
直接拉去河边扔掉
and dump it down by the river.
好吧 我还是说了吧
Okay, I'm just gonna say it--
苏菲 让奥列格
Sophie, would it kill you
把那该死的画挂你家难道会要你的命吗
to just let Oleg hang the damn painting?
你闹哪样啊 居然直接把车停在
So what, you just park the truck
范威克高速公路中间吗
in the middle of the Van Wyck Expressway?
你就不能学着点吗
Do you never learn?
我刚差点嘴碰到租车易的脚垫
I almost ate Rent-A-Truck floor mat.
卡洛琳 你要明白一点
Caroline, you get this straight--
奥列格是错的
Oleg was wrong.
还有那对奶头也大得太离谱了吧
And those nipples were way too big.
这下尴尬了
This is awkward.
你怎么会在车上
You're in the truck?
错 是你怎么会在我公寓里
No, you're in my apartment.
我们好像被车撞了
I think something hit us.
你们俩需要做伴侣心理治疗
You guys just need some couples therapy.
我来当调解员吧
I'll mediate it,
因为我曾接受过治疗
since I've had therapy myself.
虽然当时不是以伴侣身份 但希望某天能成真
Not as a couple, but hopefully someday.
我只是坐在这里等拖车来而已
I'm just sitting here waiting for the tow truck to come.
你的脖子没事吧 麦克斯
How's your neck, Max?
没什么大碍
Not so bad.
第二辆撞我们的车把第一辆车
The second car that hit us kind of knocked
撞出来的地方又撞回原位了
what the first car knocked out of place back in place.
我先说吧
I'll start.
这个女人就是一个骗子
This woman is a fraud and a liar.
我们需要多一点《奥普拉秀》的温情
Okay, well, we need a little more Oprah,
少一点《杰里·斯普林格秀》的撕逼
a little less Jerry Springer.
不许说斯普林格秀的坏话
Hey, don't dis Springer.
嘉宾休息室里的零食超好吃
They have great snacks in the green room.
你上过那个节目吗
You were on Jerry Springer?
当然 我那期名叫"我讨厌我的室友
Yeah, I was on "I hate my roommate
却又不知道怎么跟她说"
and I don't know how to tell her."
在这件事上 我和奥列格不可能谈得拢
Oleg and I are not gonna talk this thing out.
如果你们想浪费时间
If you want to waste your time,
不如直接去市中心高中教书
go teach in an inner city high school.
有个更好的办法
You know what? Even better--
我代奥列格发言
I'll do the talking for Oleg.
这样的话 麦克斯 那你替我好了
Oh, then, Max-- you be me, okay, Max?
我不知道能不能....
Oh--I don't know if--
你还想不想要剩下的牛肉了
Do you want the rest of the beef, or not?
那家伙就是个混蛋 那幅画必须扔出去
This guy is a bum, and the painting has to go.
那画蠢爆了
It's stupid.
说得太棒了 麦克斯
Really, really good, Max,
但下次记得把胸挺起来一点 像这样
but next time just arch your back a little, and, yeah.
好的
Yeah.
好的 你替我
Okay, you be me.
不要 我不喜欢现在受到勃起的威胁
No, I don't feel like getting a threatening erection right now.
但我要说的是 只要两个人决定住在一起
But I will say, anytime people move in together,
那必须相互妥协
it's a compromise.
瞧瞧麦克斯
Look at Max--
在我需要地方住的时候 她连我的马都收留了
when I needed a place to stay, she let me have my horse.
让我这么说吧 我在撕逼节目上也说过
Let me just say--and I brought this up on Springer--
我是因为那匹马才愿意收留你的
I only let you in because of the horse.
而我终于放弃抵抗
And I finally stopped putting up a fight
让麦克斯光着身子在家里四处走
and let Max walk around naked.
什么时候放弃的
When did that happen?
明天
Tomorrow.
奥列格
Oh, Oleg,
我可不想让你放弃在家裸身四处走的权利
I wouldn't want you to give up walking around naked.
我是说 只要你别坐在白色的东西上就行
I mean, as long as you don't sit down on anything white.
情有可原
Makes sense.
没人会喜欢软椅上有一朵巧克力色的菊花
Nobody likes a chocolate starfish on an ottoman.
得分 苏菲
Point, Sophie.
我赢了 各位
I'm winning, everybody!
这是治疗
Well, it's therapy.
没有所谓的输赢
There are no winners and losers.
输了的废柴才会说这种话
Sounds like something a loser would say.
奥列格
You know, Oleg,
其实整件事跟那幅白痴画无关
this isn't about that silly little painting.
只是...
It's just, uh,
短时间内有太多变动了
a lot of change in a short amount of time...
人家好害怕
I'm so scared.
苏菲
Sophie,
其实我才不在乎我的东西 有你就够了
I don't care about my stuff, as long as I have you.
我们干了什么好事
What did we just do?
本来都搞分手了 现在又被我们劝复合了
We had them apart, and now we just put them back together.
都怪你
You did that.
谁让你不懂何时闭嘴
You don't know when to butt out.
杰里说的哦
Jerry's words.